<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="title">Things to do in Amravati</string>
    <string name="landmark_image_view_descripsion">landmark image</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail">DetailActivity</string>
    <string name="view_page_title_landmarks">Landmarks</string>
    <string name="view_page_title_nature">Nature</string>
    <string name="view_page_title_restaurant">Restaurant</string>
    <string name="view_page_title_festivals">Festivals</string>
    <string name="navratri">Navaratri</string>
    <string name="ganesh_chaturth">Ganesh Chaturthi</string>
    <string name="holi">Holi</string>
    <string name="raksha_bandhan">Raksha Bandhan</string>
    <string name="raksha_bandhan_desc">Raksha Bandhan, also abbreviated to Rakhi, is the Hindu festival that celebrates brotherhood and love. It is celebrated on the full moon in the month of Sravana in the lunar calendar.The word Raksha means protection, whilst Bandhan is the verb to tie.</string>
    <string name="holi_desc">Holi is the Hindu festival that welcomes the Spring and celebrates the new life and energy of the season. Although Holi has religious roots, not much religious activity is involved in its celebration.</string>
    <string name="ganesh_chaturthi_desc">Ganesh is also known by the names Ganapati, Ekadanta, Vinayaka, Pillaiyar and Heramba. Irrespective of what Hindu tradition, he is still one of the most popular deities for worship.</string>
    <string name="navratri_desc">Navaratri (nine nights) is one of the greatest Hindu festivals. It symbolises the triumph of good over evil. Navratri takes place at the beginning of October around harvest time and, as the name implies, this festival is celebrated for nine days. Navratri is also known as Durga Puja.</string>
    <string name="ambadevi_temple">Shri Ambadevi Temple</string>
    <string name="ambadevi_temple_desc">It\'s an ancient Hindu temple. Located in the heart of Amravati, Ambadevi temple is reckoned as one of the oldest temples of the region. The principal deity of the temple is Goddess Ambadevi, incarnations of goddess Durga. According to historical records, Krishna got married to her in Ambadevi temple.</string>
    <string name="maltekli">Maltekdi</string>
    <string name="maltekli_desc"><![CDATA[Maltekdi is a beautiful hilltop in the central of Amravati city . This place is best for morning/evening walk, having a slant height due to hill. We will have a clear & beutiful view of the city from a hill top with fresh air. It has play equipments for childrens as well as free gymnasium equipments for adults for both male & female. It is place for rejoice & excercise]]></string>
    <string name="hvpm">HVPM</string>
    <string name="hvpm_desc">Hanuman Vyayam Prasarak Mandal (HVPM) is a premier institute in India in physical training. It was set up by Mr Anant Vaidya and Mr Ambadas Vaidya around 1914. Earlier it was referred as Hanuman Akhada.</string>
    <string name="amravati_university">Amravati University</string>
    <string name="amravati_university_desc">The university was established on 1 May 1983. The university campus is spread over an area of 225 hectares, and the university is home to 20 post-graduate departments offering 25 courses in different disciplines.</string>
    <string name="melghat">MelGhat Tiger Reserve</string>
    <string name="melghat_desc">Melghat tiger reserve is great place to visit and have a close encounter with nature with beautiful roads and pleasant wether with variety of animals u can also visit a hill station chikhaldara to enjoy sunsets and beautiful whether.</string>
    <string name="fort">Gavilgarh Fort</string>
    <string name="fort_desc">Gawilgadh Fort is situated at Chikhaldara hill station. Fort built in 1200 century went in the hands of Mughals for 260 years and then with British.It is property maintained by archeological serve Department of India. This fort have very large area and its internal planing is a good sample of security measures that time was taken. There is a palace and a tank inside. It\'s a good place to visit.</string>
    <string name="bamboo_garden">Bamboo Garden</string>
    <string name="bamboo_garden_desc">This is first \'bamboo garden\' of india in Amravati City. Amaravati residents will enjoy touring in this bamboo forest and this garden.Maharashtra is the highest bamboo growing State and its largest and most famous bamboo nursery is known as Vadali. Vadali lake and nearby areas with hillocks are located at a small distance from Amaravati city and this is a forest area. It is where Vadali bamboo nursery is located.</string>
    <string name="upper_wardha_dam">Upper Wardha Dam</string>
    <string name="upper_wardha_dam_desc">This dam is located at Simbhora village near Morshi. It\'s approximately 60 km away from Amravati. It\'s major dam and lifeline of Amravati. It is mostly visited by peoples during rainy season and specially when its overflowing.</string>
    <string name="wadali_talao">Wadali Talao</string>
    <string name="wadali_talao_desc">Wadali lake garden or Wadali talao is the only place in Amravati city where one can spend time with family and kids. This place is well connected with roads and its not far from city or almost in the city and one can go by autoriksha and bus.</string>
    <string name="rajkamal_square">Rajkamal Square</string>
    <string name="rajkamal_square_desc">Rajkamal Square was named after the famous Rajkamal Theater, where the plays were staged those days. Now we have a Cenema Theater at that place. This place is the heart of the city and you will get really nice street food here.</string>
    <string name="spice_kitchen_hotel">Spice Kitchen</string>
    <string name="spice_kitchen_hotel_desc">Spice Kitchen is essentially the best Restaurant you can go out to! The Indian and oriental food options are their speciality and you\'d get a reasonably decent range of options at the adjoining bar too.</string>
    <string name="test_of_south">Taste Of South</string>
    <string name="test_of_south_desc">Good ambience and nice food quality. Great service, too. Price is also very reasonable looking at all the features. The quality and quantity of food is perfect. Thali of this restaurant is also very good.</string>
    <string name="mehfil_hotel">Hotel Grand Mehfil</string>
    <string name="mehfil_hotel_desc">My wife and I stayed in this hotel for 2 nights recently for attending a conference. The facade and look of the hotel look attractive and the quality if surely very good for a comparatively  city like Amravati</string>
</resources>
